我会这样回答你的问题
This is how I would answer your question,
曼奇尼先生
Mr. Mancini.
你怎么敢这样  先生
How dare you, sir?
你有私人生活吗
Do you have a personal life?
你有配偶吗
Do you have a spouse?
你知道把你的私人生活
Do you know what it would be like
像这样摆到台面上来说
to have your personal life spilled
会是什么样吗
across the stage like this?
被直播
Broadcasted
让你的朋友  同事
into the homes of your friends, your workmates,
你女儿的同学在家里都能看到
your daughter's friends at school?
你知道那会是怎样吗
Do you know what that would be like?
夫人  我只想报道
Ma'am, I'm only reporting...
如果我丈夫的不忠与我的工作
It would be one thing if my job
相关的话  那就另当别论了
had anything to do with my husband's infidelity.
我难以想象什么工作能跟那扯上关系
I'm not even sure what job that would be.
不过那样你的问题至少算是切题
But your question would at least then be pertinent.